Yes, we get superpowers!
Superpowers!
There's a monster deep within your dreams.
Taking aim for your
heart so it would seem.
Stand tall and read, go to
hell and jump for paradise.
Every time dangerous, dangerous.
We like it serious, serious, oh.
Looking deep in the dream
there is the one in pain.
Turns out that's the one who
means the most to you today.
Adventure calls now, let's go.
The balls built between
us, they will show.
Still what we don't know.
Yes, working hard together.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
Got to dream.
Despite the rivalry.
Gotta see it through.
Believing in you.
There's even charm in failure.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
All the love and the tears.
In the world we're in.
United gently bringing up.
Our thought again, yeah.
We're the foolish ones we love.
We'll carry on till we see the light.
The sun will rise.
The greatest fight at its core.
Is against myself forevermore.
Come on, let's do it now, let's go.
The balls filled between
us, they will show.
So what we don't know.
That's what we call adventure.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
Got to dream despite the rivalry.
Gotta see it through believing in you.
There's even charm in failure.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
Superpowers.
Superpowers. Superpowers.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
Superpowers.
Yes, we're the superpowers!
Now an ingress has crooked evil
food money because wasted on you!
But that explosion is still a mystery.
We still don't know who caused that mess.
I doubt it was Straw Hat and his allies
since they were on the roof as well.
They were as likely to
kill themselves as us.
Hey Anna, there is no mystery that's
been solved during the tea party.
All lines of communication
to the venue were
jumped and I couldn't
figure out the cause.
It was probably orchestrated by
Petty and his allies. Yeah, sure.
Didn't the chicken man want
to report something, too?
Oi, oi.
Some troubling news about the Sun Pirates.
They were stationed on the East
Coast, but so done all the...
They took off!
The bunch of backstabbing
little cowards ran away!
Back homes?
Yeah, I saw them packing up myself!
Everyone on the crew!
They went back home!
Let's see.
That explains Chimbe's
actions at least. Get on.
At the tea party.
Jinbei stared Mama down,
quit the Big Mom Pirates, and said
he was joining the Straw Hats.
What?
Was he planning that all along?
Yeah.
And that's why his crew left.
He knew Mama would take
out her anger on his crew.
When Jinbei's first attempt
to leave didn't go well,
he said he'd stick around to
give his friends time to escape.
Just the kind of thoughtful
strategy you would expect from him.
Katakuri, our troops are already chasing
down Straw Hat and Buggy as we speak.
That's good.
We sent a detached force, too.
They're invading German.
In that case, Rulé, come with me.
You don't even have to ask me.
Assuming we're going to kill Straw
Hat and his friends, of course.
I will make them pay.
They abused me like some
sort of pack animal.
They even used me in
their scheme to kill Mama.
Oh, the indignity I suffered.
You'll have your revenge.
I'll take Straw Hat's head personally.
I've seen enough.
He needs to be eliminated quickly.
If we let him survive, he may become
an even greater threat to Mama.
Everyone, hurry!
You've got to get out of the city!
Smoothie.
Run as fast and far as you can!
Bad timing.
What do you mean, run? What's happening?
I am telling you, just get out of here!
You're kidding me.
I can't reach Lord Judge or
Master Ichichi on the snail.
This looks really bad.
What's happening?
Why are the Big Mom Pirates here?
Where is it?
Where is the wedding cake?
Her hunger pangs have come back already!
The last one was the other day!
How are we supposed to live like this?
She never got to eat cake.
As soon as she remembered that,
she must have gone out of her mind!
Mama's got someone in her hand!
Hmm.
It's too late for him.
Big Brother Opera!
Hey!
Wake up, you idiot!
Please don't tell me
Mama stole your lifespan!
Wake up!
He chose to do this.
It was his atonement.
He tried to stop her.
But we need to make sure we
don't suffer the same fate.
We can't just stand
here and take our legs.
Where's my cake?
Give it to me!
Let's pick up the pace.
They'll be coming after us soon enough.
No fair.
You don't get to ride on Jinbei
and boss us around, lazy thump.
Stop griping.
Nani can do whatever she wants,
because she's cute. Very cute.
Delicate, too.
as nami said pursuers will surely find
us so we must break haste don't worry
i know a trick just keep going straight
if we cut through the seducing woods
we'll be back at the sunny in no time
at all you
all know
what to do the only
way to stop mama's rampage is to give
her whatever Whatever food she's craving!
We need wedding cake.
Only the finest.
Where is the head chef?
He's the only one who can make a
cake as impressive as the last one!
Uh, well, uh, that's gonna be tricky.
Struzan saved everyone's life with
his ability, but when he came down,
he screwed up the landing, big time!
I'm sorry he's going to
need several days to recover
We've got to come up with a new
plan before sweet city is destroyed
But there's no stopping
mama when she's like this
We can't just let her
rampage through the capital
what the he's got a plan he'll save us all
you can always count
on pedos Patty Get off!
Mama!
The wedding cake you seek,
it's not actually gone!
Or, more accurately, we take
the second one just in case. Ah!
Press, no!
You can't lie.
She'll find out.
It's made from only the
finest ingredients, of course.
Why, you lick your lips
at the very sight of it.
It's the greatest cake
the world has ever seen.
I really wanted you to have
it, but wouldn't you know?
Those insufferable Straw Hats
stole it in the lickety-split.
Now they're heading to the
southwest coast trying to escape.
A lickety-fiasco.
They have my wedding cake?
That's right, the Straw
Hat's took it, Elik.
It seems she understands
me to some extent.
If she goes after Straw Hat, it's
like killing two birds with one stone.
Is he really gonna pull this off?
If you are lying you'll pay.
Don't think I won't
take your lifespan, boy.
Zeus!
Huh?
You're coming.
Mamma!
I'll have my cake.
Mamma.
Mamma, mamma.
Mamma, mamma!
No, I am in for it now.
Even if mama does wipe out the straw
hats, the cake I promised isn't real.
What should I do?
Well, it seems like a good idea.
I don't have a lick of hope; I'm as good
as dead, but you bought some time at least.
We've got to find someone to make
that cake, otherwise we're all dead.
Well, we're licked then—think
about this for a sec—would you?
Struzan is obviously our best chef by far.
And it took him days
to complete that cake.
Plus all
of the rare ingredients we acquired
in our raids are all used up.
With Struzan still in a coma, there's
no one else who can bake the cake.
Mama never
even tasted it.
In other words, we must create the
perfect cake from her imagination.
her imagination What does that even mean?
If she doesn't get the cake
she's built up in her head,
Mama will reject it and
continue to rampage.
It's hopeless.
Who can make such a fantastical creation?
No matter what, it seems this
island is doomed to be destroyed.
What lies beyond that is unknown.
Anything I can do to help.
Pudding!
Lady Pudding!
Love the dress!
In case you didn't notice, the
wedding cake was chocolate chiffon.
When it comes to chocolate, I'm
every bit as good as the head chef.
And when it comes to chiffon cakes,
our sister lives up to her name.
If we team up, then we
can make the perfect cake.
We don't have to die!
Yeah, but chiffon's our enemy now.
She ran off with veggie.
I'll just have to make her do it.
That's our evil pudding.
What lady pudding's acting like a thug!
One more thing.
The ingredients won't be a problem.
They were originally
delivered to Chocolatown,
since Cacao Island is the
gateway to our territory.
We didn't use them all, so
we still have supplies there.
Press, here's the plan.
Once Mama eliminates the Straw
Hats, lead her to Chocolatown.
I'll end this matter myself.
How lickety-splendent of you to offer!
Sanji humiliated me, bastard.
To think that you were
hiding such a beautiful eye.
If Mama can crush that insect, then
I don't mind rewarding her with cake.
You can't escape for long, Sanji.
Something wrong?
My heart just skipped a beat.
I guess some cutie was
talking about me as usual.
There they are, the seducing ones!
You sure we're going to be okay in there?
It kind of sucked last time.
Hey, you see that?
Oh, Pinky, Pink, silly.
But I'm worried.
You're hurt.
Maybe keep your branches off
that for a while, Lady Tree.
I'm sorry, but your sides will
stick together soon enough.
Just like the two of us, right?
I'm in a world of pain here.
What?
Really?
Hey!
King Balm!
I thought you were dead.
I'm so happy!
It's good to see you, tree!
Lucky us!
Leave me alone!
Go away!
I'll make you pay, Doomcoffs!
Kingy!
My tree!
Keep going straight and don't look back!
Son of a bitch!
Nami, how do you have that?
I thought they took Mola's
Beaver Card away from you.
They thought so too.
Turns out, I cut it in half.
Wow, smart!
This tree is swift.
And since he's the master of the seducing
woods, he can cut a path straight through.
All right, tree, head for the
sunny, full speed! Go, tree!
You guys are like a
plague upon this kingdom!
My only consolation is
not helping you live.
Sorry, what was that?
Thanks, Adnasi!
You better not talk back to Nami!
Okay, targets are
sighted and within range.
Full speed ahead!
Look behind us! Enemies!
Now charge!
Step one in, King Bells!
I'm going to spawn since I can!
You get caught and I'll
tear you apart at the scene!
You scare me.
Something just passed over our heads.
Did you know that laugh already?
I've come for my wedding day.
Let's make mom.
Where is it?
Meanwhile, near the Juice River,
on the outskirts of Sweet City...
Oh!
I see it!
The Juice River.
Hopefully the shark submerge
will still be moored over there.
It's up ahead?
Uh-oh!
Why is the whole river
filled with heavy cream?
Wow! Yummy!
No way!
I gotta try!
It's incredible!
I find it hard to believe
that the debris made it
this far when the Whole
Cake Shit toppled over.
It's so good!
I'm not sure how to
free the shark submerge.
Wait, Chopper!
I think Mom's gonna
reach us in a second now!
Why did she come out here?
Something's wrong.
Did you get a look at her?
Don't tell me it's her hunger pains.
Where's my wedding cake Straw Hat?
Hurry up, King Balm!
Shake her off!
The cow!
You'll be skewered!
The Spear of Elbeth shall pierce you!
Wait, Elbeth?
Everyone get ready!
Let me go!
Oh, my God.
Where is my cake?
That's...like the special
move those Giants did!
But why?
Hey, King-Bomb!
Forgive me, Mama, my branches are tied!
These awful pirates are
forcing me to do this!
No, here she comes again!
Come on, let's fight!
Hey, Kingbaum, who's that tree back there?
Was that your girlfriend?
Oh, Kingy, thanks, Dial.
But I'm worried, you're hurt.
Kingy!
Lady Tree!
Nein, she's my tree-on-sing!
How romantic!
We were going to set up roots together!
It was destiny!
Then live!
Live for her sake!
You want to see her again,
don't you? Fight! Don't die!
Ya'll do it!
For future I have to! Then run!
Run like the wind!
Once we're safe, you can be together!
For today and tomorrow!
In sweet matrimony forevermore!
Yaaaaaaah!
Planetry!
Nice.
She's diabolical.
That's our doggy!
I want wedding cake!
Okay!
Looks like it's my turn! Ruby! No!
I have an idea!
On my case...
I said my turn!
Now!
Black ball!
Lightning, love! Other lightning!
It's up!
Got it!
Mama!
Bombay!
Have you lost your mind, Zeus?
Great, he's totally spaced out. Mama!
We're going to lose them in the woods!
Get up!
Come back here with my cake!
Once we reach the woods,
we'll have the edge.
We have King Bound with us, after all.
The master of the forest.
It's King Bound! He's born!
Boy, he's in a hurry!
I wonder what gives!
Out of my way!
Awesome!
How far?
That's sandy.
Everyone!
Step aside! Sunny!
Look! Guys!
It's the sunny! Really?
Right to the coast.
It's a straight shot.
You are so spotless!
Nabi, way to go!
As long as Big Mom isn't riding
on Zeus, we'll stay safe.
The cloud's name is Zeus?
Yes, Big Mom created him
from a piece of her soul.
Yep, that's me, all right.
Act Lobby is Zeus! He's here! What now?
Be strong, be wary.
Hey, can I get some more of those
yummy little thunder clouds?
Huh?
The black balls?
Were they tasty?
Yeah, they were rich and tingly
and went down really smooth.
Best I ever had.
So, can I get some more?
Clouds think clouds are yummy?
You're so fluffy.
Gimme, gimme, gimme. Pretty please?
You can eat later.
Forget that and let us ride you.
I can't.
You see, only Mama can because I
contain part of her soul. That's lame.
Cloud, you suck. Boring.
If you can't give us a
ride, how about this?
How would you like to become my servant?
Gladly!
She's talking to the Cloud, not you.
Then I'll use my blackball technique
to summon snacks for you every day!
Huh? Really?
What to do?
I'm not the only one switching sides.
You know, it was so cool when you got
all big and covered up the whole sky.
You could be the star of the show.
Oh, wow, you think?
Mama never compliments me
like that or gives me snacks.
Where is my cake?
Listen up, seducing wards.
No!
Let's not get past to the coast!
She's...angry!
The forest got annoying again!
What's the deal?
Can't we just kick the
trees out of the way?
I wish,
but if we rampage around in there,
all the trees will move and we
won't know where we are anymore!
Indeed.
The purpose of this
forest is to disorient.
Unfortunately, Mama
outranks my own authority.
Who's yet?
I'm coming! Make me free!
We're back! That's right!
Run for your love and for your future!
We're Mama's orders! Stop them!
I'm not going to the
Lumberyard, not today!
Why are you doing this team now?
Almost there! Keep pushing!
Find something to hang on to! Tree!
Nice work!
And Gum-Gum!
Wow, that's convenient.
Why is it so hot? No.
Dammit.
Pickles got real big.
He must be mad.
Hey, King Bomb, stop.
Tell me, why did you betray Mama?
It's complicated, okay?
It burns!
What should we do?
Are we trying to crush us?
Come on, King Balm, run away!
Go, King Balm!
Hurry up!
You have to do it for your fiancé!
Let's go! He can't move!
Run away!
Nami, come on!
Get back!
He'll burn you, Karoo, too! Nami!
That's me!
I! I!
Weee!
King Belf, no!
You can't!
Ah!
Strawhead,
give me.
my cake.
Where's Betty?
We'll catch up to him soon.
I noticed there's a fire
in the seducing woods.
I think Mama is fighting there.
Mont d 'Or, this is Barrel
in the Mirror World.
We have 10,000 troops ready.
Perfect.
We'll be in touch.
Candy. Biscuit. Nuts.
Prepare battleships from your islands.
And keep an eye on the southwest coast.
where the Straw Hat ship is moored.
Do not let them raise anchor.
Yes, sir!
Your blockade will be the
first hurdle they face.
Tart ships from Flavor Island and Liqueur
Island will be positioned further out.
Get ready and remain
on standby at the port.
Move in once you get a warning
signal from the Territory Slugs.
Roger.
They may have avoided the Slugs on the
way in, but this time they're dead.
The forest is noisy today.
That's no surprise.
Mama is chasing down the Straw
Hats personally, so it's unlikely,
no, impossible that they'll make it here.
A safe bet.
So, uh, why are we setting up an ambush?
Just in case.
Hey, you get the Dark tanks,
couldn't just let me go. Fire!
We're nearly at the coast, though.
Banshee, stop! Whoa!
You startled me!
Sorry, doll. Back off.
Lady or not, I will shoot you.
I'm only here to talk to Chiffon.
I need to see her immediately.
Chiffon, where are you?
Pudding?
What's all this about? There you are.
There's a problem only you can help with.
Mama's been hit with
another hunger pang attack.
This time, she wants a wedding cake.
You said a hunger pang attack?
Well, because the cake that she wants
happens to be chocolate chiffon.
So you understand why I need you?
Hmm.
Because my chiffon cakes are
the best cakes. That's right.
And my chocolate is the best.
So if we combine our talents,
we could make a cake that
easily satisfies Mama's craving.
Hopefully before any more people die.
We have to stop her now!
Please, Chiffon, you must!
I'm sorry, Pudding.
I'm leaving this family
just like Lola did.
I can't be burdened by Mama anymore,
or worry about the people here either.
She's done. Now go. You heard her.
You've got it wrong, huh?
I don't care about saving Mama.
And I don't care what
happens to Toto Land either.
I need to stop Mama before it's too late.
I know she'll kill him.
She'll murder Sanji and his friends too!